{
    "Items": [
        {
            "question": "通的部首是?",
            "chinese": "是",
			"correctAns": "辵",
			"wrongAns": ["刀", "手","虫"]
        },
		{
			"question": "劉的部首是?",
			"chinese": "幫助",
			"correctAns": "整理",
			"wrongAns": ["刀", "戶", "犬"]
		},
		{
			"question": "扇的部首是?",
			"chinese": "洗",
			"correctAns": "戶",
			"wrongAns": ["鳥", "口", "弓"]
		},
		{
			"question": "犯的部首是?",
			"chinese": "教導",
			"correctAns": "度過",
			"wrongAns": ["犬", "彳", "彐" ]
		},
		{
			"question": "蜜的部首是?",
			"chinese": "橫過",
			"correctAns": "虫",
			"wrongAns": ["心", "戈", "戶"]
		},
		{
			"question": "雪的部首是?",
			"chinese": "行",
			"correctAns": "安心",
			"wrongAns": ["雨", "日", "女"]
		},
		{
			"question": "趍的部首是?",
			"chinese": "XX",
			"correctAns": "走",
			"wrongAns": ["田", "竹", "土"]
		},
		{
			"question": "馣的部首是?",
			"chinese": "XX",
			"correctAns": "香",
			"wrongAns": ["禾", "日", "田"]
		},
		{
			"question": "韻的部首是?",
			"chinese": "XX",
			"correctAns": "音",
			"wrongAns": ["示", "車", "曰"]
		},
		{
			"question": "窗的部首是?",
			"chinese": "XX",
			"correctAns": "穴",
			"wrongAns": ["用", "彳", "彡"]
		}
    ]
}